like say welcome brothers and sisters to
another Wednesday question and answer
well we open up with the Ten
Commandments that God commanded the
whole world to keep brother James yes
sir and God spake all these words saying
I am the Lord thy God which have brought
thee out of the land of Egypt out of the
house of bondage Thou shalt have no
other gods before me thou shall not make
unto thee any Graven image or any
likeness of anything that is in heaven
above
or that is in the earth beneath or that
is in the water under the Earth Thou
shalt not bow down thyself to them nor
serve them for I the Lord thy God am a
jealous God visiting the iniquity of the
fathers upon the children unto the third
and fourth generation of them that hate
me and showing Mercy unto thousands of
them that love me and keep my
Commandments Thou shalt not take the
name of the Lord thy God in vain for the
Lord will not hold him Guiltless that
taketh his name in vain remember the
Sabbath day to keep it holy six days
shalt thou labor and do all thy work but
the seventh day is the Sabbath of the
Lord thy God in it Thou shalt not do any
work thou nor thy son nor thy daughter
thy man's servant nor thy maid servant
nor thy cattle nor thy stranger that is
within thy gates for in six days the
Lord made Heaven and Earth the sea and
all that in them is and resteth the
seventh day wherefore the Lord blessed
the Sabbath day and hollowed it honor
thy father and thy mother that thy days
may be long upon the land which the Lord
thy God giveth thee Thou shalt not kill
Thou shalt not commit adultery Thou
shalt not steal Thou shalt not bear
false witness against thy neighbor Thou
shalt not covet thy neighbor's house
Thou shalt not covet thy neighbor's wife
nor nor his man's servant nor his maid
servant nor his Ox nor his ass nor
anything that is thy neighbors I read
Exodus 20:
1-17 may the Lord add a blessing to the
reading of this word in Jesus name we
pray amen
amen so here on question and answer you
can ask us a question and we'll answer
it according to the King James Bible and
if we cannot find the answer we will
seek further counsel to bring you an
answer at a later time
keep in mind that all questions that we
will not answer are the vague and long
scripture questions as well as questions
of debate we are not here to debate we
are here to spread the true Gospel of
Jesus so please be direct with your
questions so we can be as direct with
our answers out of the King James Bible
nor the Bibles or books will be
acknowledged on this program also keep
in mind this is a live stream so feel
free to send in your questions that
pertain to everlasting life we just ask
that you keep your scriptures to a two
scripture maximum but let me introduce
to you the family that's on the panel
this evening brother Jerome rce and
peace Brother Julius good evening
everybody brother Dre good evening
brother James good evening everyone
sister Deborah good evening brother Sean
good evening and we have the guest
caller with us and I'm brother Cornell
sister Deborah what is our first
question of the evening uh yes uh there
are several held over questions that
will be answered first before getting
into tonight's Q&A so uh read the Bible
daily as in Ezekiel 7 verse
22 what is the secret
place brother Julius in light us on this
secret place in Ezekiel
7:22 let's go and read that brother
James my face will I turn also from them
and they shall pollute my secret place
for the robber shall enter into it and
defile
it now this is uh h a a prophecy and the
secret place was when the Romans came
into the inner sanctuary of the temple
and took Jerusalem down so the secret
place is the inner sanctuary of the
temple that's all I
got all right thank you brother that
light was right on point as we move on
to our next question yes uh philosophy
asked in Genesis 15 verse 10 and 11 why
did Abram not cut birds in half and what
does the next verse of the vultures mean
I have seen different interpretations
and wanted to know the actual context to
these two
verses Genesis 1510 and 11 brother Dre
what you say go read that and we'll deal
with it go ahead and read it when you
get it brother James and he took unto
him all these and divided them in the
midst and laid each piece one against
another but the birds divided he not and
when the fils came down upon the
carcasses Abram drove them
away it didn't say why he did that why
he did not cut the birds in half it did
not say in that
passage um in terms of
vultures in verse 11 says and when the
fils came down upon the carcasses Abram
drove them away when you read in other
interpretations or other
translations of the scripture you get
where it says vultures we at the Israel
of God we read out of the King James
version of the Bible and in the KJV it
says files not vultures and the foul is
just about anything that
flies I hope that
helped all right thank you for that
brother we hope that answered that
question our next one
yes uh we can talk right here as if
we're not to talk or if we are not to do
pleasure and find pleasure in this show
is this show but
watch it on Saturday so if we're not to
do pleasure and find pleasure in this
show but watch on Saturday is that wrong
and I watch the camps talk about things
am I wrong doing it on
Saturday brother juliia share some
knowledge let's go to scripture what he
says not doing your pleasure Isaiah the
58th chapter and we gonna read one verse
and we're gonna see the hook in this the
differen is in in this right here James
Isaiah 58 verse3 please if thou turn
away thy foot from the Sabbath from
doing thy pleasure on my holy day and
call the Sabbath of delight the holy of
the Lord honorable and shall honor him
not doing thine own ways nor finding
thine own pleasure nor speaking thine
own
words now answer is no you're not wrong
for watching this program on a Saturday
because you are watching the Lord's
program you are being edified on his day
and you're calling the Sabbath of the
light you're keeping it holy and you're
you're calling it a delight it is not
your pleasure per se the things outside
of the Sabbath but within the Sabbath
because the Lord say you call my Sabbath
a delight holy so you're doing the
pleasure of the Lord that he desires you
to do meditation prayer doing good on
his day so that's the different between
Your Personal Pleasures outside of the
Sabbath day like going fishing or or
going to work or washing your car so
you're doing what's pleasing to the Lord
on his day so you're not wrong for doing
this as opposed to what other camps are
talking about if we're talking about the
football games and the basketball games
that's our words but we ought to
meditate and that's something that we
all have to work on meditating on
keeping the Lord's Day holy and U uh
doing what's pleasing to him that's all
I got all right and we can always take
pleasure in hearing the truth right
brother amen all right hope that
answered your question as we move on to
our next one moving on Malicia cure as
in Luke 3 verse 23 why is as was
supposed in
parenthesis all right ain't that Luke
let's go there brother James to that
Luke 3 and 23 and where it has as was
supposed in par es the guest caller take
it from
there Luke 3 and 23 says and Jesus
himself began to be about 30 years of
age being as was supposed the son of
Joseph which was the son of
heli okay the thing is uh it's
supposedly because Jesus don't have a
biological
father let's go into Isaiah the 7th
chapter
read verses 13 and
14 Isaiah 7: 13 and4 says and he said
hear ye now oh House of David is it a
small thing for you to weary men but
will ye weary My God
also th therefore the Lord himself shall
give you a sign Behold a virgin shall
conceive and bear a son and shall call
his name Emmanuel
okay so it was written that a virgin
shall conceive and she going to have a
son going to call his name Emanuel so
let's go into Matthew the first
chapter and pursue this read verses 18
to through
23 Matthew 1:
18-23 say now the birth of Jesus Christ
was on this wise when as his mother Mary
was espouse to Joseph before they came
together she was found with child of the
Holy Ghost then Joseph her husband being
a just man and not willing to make her a
public example was minded to put her
away privately but while he thought on
these things behold the angel of the
Lord appeared unto him in a dream saying
Joseph thou son of David fear not to
take unto thee Mary thy wife for that
which is conceived in her is of the Holy
Ghost and she shall bring forth a son
and thou shalt call his name Jesus for
he shall save his people from their sins
now all this was done that it might be
fulfilled which was spoken of the Lord
by the prophet saying Behold a virgin
shall be with child and shall bring
forth a son and they shall call his name
Emmanuel which being interpreted is god
with
us so now when the uh uh uh Mary that's
why Joseph was going to put it away
because she ain't laid with nobody she
come up pregnant but then isai already
said that uh uh virgin shall conceive
and she have a son you know and uh uh uh
called his name Emmanuel which mean God
is with us how is that let's go into
Hebrews the 10th chapter read verse one
and Skip down and read verse four and
five Hebrews 10 and verse one says for
the law having a shadow of good things
to come and not the very image of the
things can never with those sacrifices
which they offered year by year
continually make the comers there unto
perfect verse four and five says for it
is not possible that the blood of blood
of bus and of goats should take away
sins wherefore when he cometh into the
world he saith sacrifice an offering
thou wouldest not but a body H has thou
prepared me so now Jesus was God before
he was a man but in order to come and
die for man he had to have something
could that could die through the father
prepared a body for him and he took that
body over and the angel came and planted
this body into Mary his mother now let's
go one last place let's go into Luke
verse chapter we're going to read verse
26 and
27 then we're going to skip
down okay Luke 1: 26 and 27 says and in
the sixth month the angel Gabriel was
sent from God unto a city G of Galilee
named Nazareth to a virgin espouse to a
man whose name was Joseph of the House
of David and the virgin's name was Mary
uhhuh now skip down and read verse 30
and 30 30 and
31 okay verse 30 says and the angel said
unto her fear not Mary for thou has
found favor with God and behold Thou
shalt conceive in thy womb and bring
forth a son and shalt call his name
Jesus now so now being now she had never
laid with a
man and so Jesus which was God when he
took on his body and was impregnated
then that mean that God was with us now
when they told when the angel told her
she was she was uh uh uh go that she was
pregnant look what she told this Angel
skip now and read verse
34 then said Mary unto the angel how
shall this be seeing I know not a
man so how am how am I pregnant and
going to have this child you want me to
call Jesus being that they ain't never
had
sex that's why it said I suppose to be
the son of Joseph because Jesus didn't
have no biological father a body was
prepared for him he took it over the
angel came and implanted it in the
woman's womb and he went the full nine
months and he was born as a man and when
he was
born God was with us even though he was
man that's all I have to say
all right thank you for that hope that
answered their question as we move on to
our next one our next question Zion
asked for you to explain Mark 16 verse 9
it says Jesus was risen early the first
day of the week which is
Sunday all right brother Dre what you
say let's look at that passage let's go
to Mark 16 and read verse
n now when Jesus was risen early the
first day of the week he appeared first
to Mary Magdalene out of whom he had
cast Seven
Devils now if you read that and put a
comma right there at risen it would read
like this now when Jesus was
risen early the first day of the week he
appeared to Mary
Magdalene out of whom he had cast out
Seven Devils he didn't cast them out
then he's just describing what he did in
the
past now let's go and look at it again
let's go to uh Matthew
28 and read verse one Matthew 28 and
verse
one go ahead end in the end of the
Sabbath as it began to Dawn towards the
first day of the week Came Mary
Magdalene and the other Mary to see the
seler now here Mary coming at the end of
the Sabbath as it began to Dawn toward
the first day of the week skip down they
run into the Angels skip down to verse
five go ahead and the angel answered and
said unto the woman fear not ye for I
know that ye seek Jesus which was
crucified go ahead he is not here for He
Is Risen as he said come see the place
where the Lord lay so when they came
there he had already
risen he it wasn't that he was there as
it dawned toward the first day of the
week but let's look at it one other
place let's go to John 20 and read verse
one John 20 and verse
one go ahead brother the first day of
the week cometh Mary Magdalene early
when it is when it was yet dark unto the
Suppa and seen the stone taken away from
the supplier so Mary came while it was
yet dark it was still
dark upon the first day of the week now
look they say that Jesus died Good
Friday and he rose Easter
Sunday and Jesus gave a sign he said
just like Jonas was in the belly of the
well for three days and three nights so
shall the son of man be the heart of the
earth you cannot get three days and
three nights from Friday
evening to Sunday
morning he had already risen on Sunday
so you really can't count that do the
counting do the math it does not work he
did did not rise on the first day of the
week I hope that
helps all right thank you for that
brother as we move on to our next
question moving on Mrs Wade asked for
you to explain John 19 verse
24 where the scripture
says uh the soldier knew the prophecy of
Jesus clothing are are they
Israelites all right brother Jerome what
you got to say let's go read it St John
Chapter 19 Verse
24 they said therefore among themselves
let us not rended but cast lots for it
whose it shall be that the SE that the
scripture might be fulfilled which saith
they parted my reignment among them and
for my vesture they did cast lots these
things therefore the soldiers
did okay now uh the soldiers that was uh
doing this talking they weren't
Israelites they were they were Gentiles
even even Romans okay
now they didn't know what the prophecy
was okay so these soldiers they were
just concerned
about having that garment that Jesus had
on so they cast lots for it and whoever
won a lot that's who got the Garment and
that's all they was really concerned
about but this was done not because they
knew about the prophecy it was done so
that when they do it it will fulfill
what was written by the prophets that
they was going to say hey they going to
cast lots for it and they going to part
his garments and that had to be done so
that the scriptures could be fulfilled
not not that they knew about that
prophecy okay uh let's go read verse 23-
24 okay 23- 24 says then the soldiers
when they crucified Jesus took his
garments and made four parts to every
Soldier a part and also his coat now the
coat was without seam woven from the top
throughout out they said therefore among
themselves let us not Rend it but cast
lots for it whose it shall be that the
scripture might be fulfilled which
sayith they parted my reignment among
them and for my vesture they did cast
lots these things therefore the soldiers
did that's all I
got all right thank you for that brother
as we move on to our next question
moving on Jennifer Love says what is the
scripture that tells us that our purpose
what our purpose is in this life a lot
of scriptures can tell you what your
purpose should be because the Lord
himself said his heart's desires that
all would repent and come into the
knowledge of god let's go to Mark 12
Mark the 12th
chapter and when you get there brother
at that Mark 12 let's here out of Jesus
mouth what he said here because she want
to know what is her purpose in this life
go ahead brother Mark 12 beginning where
28 okay it says and one of the scribes
came and having heard them reasoning
together and perceiving that he had
answered them well asked him which is
the first commandment of
all and Jesus answered him the first of
all the Commandments is here oh Israel
the Lord our God is one Lord the first
thing you got the first thing you got to
do is hear have an ear to hear go ahead
brother and thou shalt love the Lord thy
God with all thy heart and with all thy
soul and with all thy mind and with all
thy strength this is the first
commandment go ahead and the second is
like namely this thou shal love thy
neighbor as thy myselfself there is none
other commandment greater than these in
the next verse he got tell you that
there's no no other God but one go ahead
and the scrib said unto him well Master
thou has said the truth for there is one
God and there is none other but he go
ahead and to love him with all the heart
and with all the understanding and with
all the soul and with all the strength
and to love his neighbor as himself self
is more than all whole burnt offerings
and sacrifices what did Jesus say in
that last verse and when Jesus saw that
he answered discreetly he said unto him
Thou Art not far from the kingdom of God
and no man after that dur ask him any
question so you supposed to learn it as
God you're supposed to keep all his laws
statutes and Commandments and realize
that there is only one true and living
God and and then you will see that you
also are not far from the kingdom of God
if you keep all of this now turn over to
the last place Ecclesiastes
12 because you have a job to save
yourself from this untour
[Music]
generation
Ecclesiastes verse
12 I mean chapter 12 read verse 13 and
14 this is also your purpose and your
job life go ahead let us hear the
conclusion of the whole matter fear God
and keep his Commandments for this is
the whole duty of man for God shall
bring every work into judgment with
every secret thing whether it be good or
whether it be evil and your purpose in
life is to make sure you're doing all
the good you can and not the evil so
that you can learn all the laws of God
and serve him so that you may save
yourself that is a great purpose that
you have done for yourself in this life
that's all I
get and we hope that that answers your
question as we move on to our next one
next one most love says I work on
Saturday but sometimes I switch my day
so I can be off on the Sabbath most jobs
especially warehouse jobs make you work
on
Saturday should I quit my job and find
another some personal questions that you
may ask like that we may not have an
answer for except for out of the pages
of the book but that's good that you can
switch your days sometimes and come and
partake in the Sabbath day like the Lord
say but telling you to
quit that's not uh my place to say that
to you only you know your financial
situation but let's go into Mark 12 I
mean 2 Thessalonians 3 2 Thessalonians
the 3
chapter because we'll give you some word
of God
here when you get there brother that's 2
Thessalonians 3 read that verse five and
we go skip go ahead and the Lord direct
your hearts into the love of God and
into the patient waiting for Christ yes
so sometimes you have to be patient wait
on Christ Lord see your heart desire
that you would love to keep the Sabbath
day but you got a job that doesn't allow
for that sometimes skip down and read
verse 10 for even when we were with you
this we commanded you that if any would
not work neither should ye eat so how
can we tell you to quit your job that
may be your only means and that might be
providing a living for you now let's go
over to Philippians the 4th chapter last
place Philippians 4
okay and when we get there I want you to
pick it up brother at that verse six
Philippians 4 and six go ahead be
careful for nothing but in everything by
prayer and supplication with
Thanksgiving let your request be made
known unto God so you should be sending
up some prayers letting the Lord know
that hey you would really love to be
keeping this sabbath day and you got a
job that doesn't allow for it and you
know maybe you'll be able to get you a
job that let you have you know the
weekends off so that you can partake in
the Lord's Sabbath day and read that
verse seven that'll be it and the peace
of God which passes all understanding
shall keep your hearts and Minds through
Christ Jesus so that great God right
there is the one you should pray to let
it be known your heart's desire and hey
he can fix all things cuz he's a a great
God that's all I
got let me thr we hope that yes caller
go right
ahead you know on the last of this
question she said should I quit my job
and find another I'm going to flipflop
that you find if you can find another
job you find it first then you can quit
your
job yeah that's all I have to say yeah
that was a good ad on there that's right
find you another job first then quit
your job
all right hope that answered your
question as we move on to our next one
moving on little mama Hayes asked will
the Gentiles that come into the belief
come into the kingdom of God under Jesus
Reign or will they be in their own land
learning from
Israel all right guess caller what's
going to be that situation in that
question well it's both of them and they
ain't going to be learning from Israel
because they're going to be learning for
the Lord and his Saints because he going
to be on this Earth that's when Jesus
come but to show you what I'm talking
about it's going to be both of them
let's go to
Isaiah 13 chapter read verses
11-4 okay Isaiah 13: 11-14 say and I
will punish the world for their evil and
the wicked for their iniquity and and I
will cause the arrogancy of The Proud to
cease and will lay low the
haltiner I will make a man more a
precious than fine gold even a man than
the golden wedge of ofur therefore I
will shake the heavens and the Earth
shall remove out of her place in the
Wrath of the Lord of hosts and in the
day of her Fierce anger and it shall be
as the chase roll and as a sheep that no
man taketh up they shall every man turn
to his own people and flee everyone into
his own
land now that's that's that's what's
going to happen too but you going to
have some that's going to go with Israel
just like it was a mixed multitude when
it come out of Egypt and let me show you
that also but first thing everybody
going to turn to their own people and
everybody going to go to their own land
but some
strangers are going with Israel let's go
into Ezekiel the 47th chapter we're
going to read verse 13 and 14
first Ezekiel 47: 13- 14 says thus
sayeth the Lord God this shall be the
Border whereby ye shall inherit the land
according to the 12 tribes of Israel
Joseph shall have two portions and he
shall inherit it one as well as another
concerning the which I lifted up my hand
to give it unto your fathers and this
land shall fall unto you for
inheritance and
this uhuh you finish that yes 13 and 14
yes okay now skip down to verse 21 and
read to 21 and 23
okay so shall ye divide this land unto
you according to the tribe of Israel and
it shall come to pass that ye shall
divide it by lot for an inheritance unto
you and to the strangers that sourn
among you which shall begot children
among you and they shall be unto you as
born in the country among the children
of Israel they shall have inheritance
with you among the tribes of Israel and
it shall come to pass that in what tribe
The Stranger sourth there shall ye give
him his inheritance sayeth the Lord
God okay so in some cases most people
will all turn to their own people and
everybody going to free to their own
land but you got some The Stranger
Gentiles included is going to go with
Israel and once they go then you have to
give them inheritance and inheritance
among the land or whatever trial they
find themselves so it's both of
them all I have to say
all right some good light there hope
that answers your question as we move on
to our next question uh yes next one
time out Houston asks in numbers 5:
11-31 God gave a test for a husband who
suspect his wife of cheating does this
test apply
today he what you say about that numers
five
no it does not apply today and
um we we can't read numbers 5
11 through 31 I think that's what you
have here that's a lot read but we'll
just read let's read numbers 5 15 to
18 okay number 5 15 to 18 says then
shall the man bring his wife to the
priest and he shall bring her offering
for her the 10th part of an apha of
barley meal he shall pour no oil upon it
nor put fragrances thereon for it is an
offering of jealousy an offering of
Memorial bringing iniquity to
remembrance and the priest shall bring
her near and set her before the Lord and
the priest shall take holy water in an
earn vessel and of the dust that is is
in the floor of the Tabernacle the
priest shall take and put it into the
water and the priest shall set the woman
before the Lord and uncover the woman's
head and put the offering of Memorial in
her hands which is the jealousy offering
and the priest shall have in his hand
the bitter water that causeth the curse
we don't have none of this right now we
don't have the water of purification The
Bitter Water the holy water we're not
offering uh barley and and all of those
things so the answer is
no that's all I got all right thank you
for that brother hope that answer that
question as we move on to our next one
next one Kesha being Camp as is keeping
an empty ear in your house
unclean yes call is keeping an empty ear
in your house
clean no if nothing's in it then it
ain't nothing but another pot of
vase it's the it's the ashes of the dead
people that make you unclean not the
earn itself all it is is some kind of
vessel that you can put water in and
anything else in it long as it don't
have the ashes of the dead people no
ain't nothing but another
pot all right hope that answered your
question as we move on to our next one
next one Valencia asks what is of sh
what is shadow of turny and James 1
verse 17 is given let's go James 1 and
17 let pick it up at that verse 16 James
1 read 16 and 17 and they want to know
what is no shadow of turning go ahead
brother do not Heir my beloved Brethren
every good gift and every perfect gift
is from above and cometh down from the
Father of Lights with whom is no
variableness neither shadow of turning
in whom is no variableness neither
shadow of turning no shadow of changing
let's go and uh read
Malachi Malachi the thir
chapter okay the Lord say he is the same
yesterday today and
forever so he don't have to twist and
turn on what he's safe because he is
perfect Malachi 3 read six and
S okay for I am the Lord I change not
therefore ye sons of Jacob are not
consumed even from the days of your
fathers ye are gone away from mine
ordinances and have not kept them return
unto me and I will return unto you
sayith the Lord of hosts but ye said
wherein shall we return yes so Lord is
just like he said for I am the Lord I
change not there is no shadow of turning
for him let's go into uh Hebrews 6
Hebrews the 6
chapter and when you get there let's
read that verse 13 and then we go to
skip Hebrews 6 and 13
go ahead brother for when God made
promises to Abraham because he could
swear by no greater he swear by himself
yes he swore by himself which we know he
keeps all his promises skip down to
verse 17 and go ahead we in God willing
more abundantly to show unto The Heirs
of Promise the
immutability of his counsel
confirmed it by an
oath that by two immutable things in
which it was impossible for God to lie
we might have a strong consolation who
have fled for Refuge to lay hold upon
the Hope set before us yes because the
Lord hey like you say it's impossible
for him to lie so when he said hey
there's no shadow of turning or change
he don't have to because he's God
himself and that's all I got on
that and we hope that answers your
question as we move on to our next
one the next one time out Houston asked
in the story of Esther in the Bible real
history or just an allegory for the
holiday of pum are there any record
records of Esther morai or hmon outside
of the Bible to confirm this story
brother
Julius absolutely first of all the Book
of Esther is in the first turn to the
Book of Esther brother James I'm there
these are actual people that actually
live and this was during the Persian uh
uh
Empire during the Persian Empire read
verse one just one verse go ahead what
which Which chapter Esther 1 and one
okay now it came to pass in the days of
Aer aaras this is a I'm sorry azerus
which reigned from India even unto
Ethiopia over
172 provinces so now this is accurate
history because the Bible is a history
book now I found the account of Esther
this right here is World Book
Encyclopedia the uh volume six and right
here it says if you could read it it
says Esther right here I have another
source right here this right here is
Ker's encyclopedia right here it says
right here right here it says the book
The Book of Esther so yes this happened
during um the fifth century somewhere
between the fifth and six uh 16th uh the
fifth century and Esther Mori Nehemiah
Li live all these things were done in
the 46
BC before Christ even came on the scene
now the story of the Book of Esther is a
story of perseverance faith and the
Deliverance of a people from their
enemies so pum the Lord allowed them to
have a civil day not a commandment but a
civil day to uh for the Jews to
um commemorate their victory over the
Persians
and the Persians because uh this was his
plot so that's all I got on that but um
these people actually live it is
recorded history another name for aashu
Eros is Xerxes I first you could do your
own research if it's in the Bible it
happened that's all I got
Corel all right thank you for that good
light there hope that answer their
question as we move on to our next next
one Straight Talk hul says I'm
struggling with tox toxic family can you
give me Clarity on turn the other cheek
it's been 50 years I'm tired of the
abuse and really need to keep my peace
in
check all right brother Dre what you
say I say don't let it rub off on you
but let go to Romans the 12th chapter
Romans
12 and pick it up at verse 17 Romans 12
and
17 okay Romans 12 and 17 says recompense
to no man evil for evil provide things
honest in the sight of all
men if it be possible as much as lith in
you live peaceably with all men hey if
it be possible as much as lith in you
you live peaceably with all
men sometimes you may have to set a
boundary for yourself that you don't
allow it to be crossed let's look at
something what the Lord said let's go to
Isaiah the first
chapter okay Isaiah 1 and when you get
there pick it up at verse two and we
gonna skip Isaiah 1 and verse two
it says hear oh heavens and give ear o
Earth for the Lord has spoken I have
nourished and brought up children and
they have rebelled against me imagine
that the Lord nourished and brought up
children and they rebelled against
him skip down to verse five brother go
ahead why should ye be stricken anymore
ye will revoke more and more the whole
head is sick and the whole heart
faint go ahead from the soul of the foot
even unto the head there is no soundness
in it but wounds and bruises and P and
putrifying
sores they have not been clothed neither
bound up neither mollified with ointment
now let's see what the Lord did let's go
over to one last place let's go over to
Hosea
five Hosea
5 Hosea 5 and 15 okay sometimes got to
set a
boundary and don't let it rub off on you
that you become toxic with somebody
else that book right after Daniel yeah
Hosea 5
andse go ahead brother I will go and
return to my place till they acknowledge
their offense and seek my face in their
Affliction they will seek me early hey
the Lord said IAM brought up children
they rebelled against me he said I will
go to my place till they they
acknowledge their offense and seek my
face in their Affliction they will seek
me Earth set a boundary for yourself and
don't you become toxic you stay rolling
with the
Lord that's all I got
yes sir all right thank you for that
hope that answered their question sister
Deborah are we going into new territory
with a time check uh yes uh the time is
18 and we are now into tonight's Q&A for
Wednesday January the 29th
2025 Cass Lee asks what does Cass in
Lots
mean all right so Jerome when they say
casting lots what do they mean by
that Lots is like a a raffle for
something that's wanted or chosen okay
so I want to give you two examples of
that let's go to uh Jonah the Book of
Jonah verse
one um chapter one and verse 6 and 7
okay
okay and
Jonah y Jonah chapter 1 verse 6 and 7 so
the shipmaster came to him and said unto
him what meanest thou Oh Sleeper arise
call upon thy God if so be that God will
think upon us that we perish not and
they said everyone to his fellow come
and let us cast lots that we may know
for whose cause this evil is upon us so
they cast lots and the lot fell upon
Jonah yes so everybody on the boat
they're afraid because of the tempet
tuous that's going on and the boat is
about to be Shipwrecked so they walking
whose fault is this and and so let's
cast lots and find out whose fault it is
and the lot pointed to Jonah and I'm
sure the hand the the Lord's hand was in
that so that that lck would fall on
Jonah because he the reason that all
that tempet tuous was going on all right
now let's go to uh Leviticus see another
example Leviticus the 16th chapter and
this is dealing with two
goats okay Leviticus the 16th chapter
and read verse
8-10 okay Leviticus 16: 8-10 say says
and Aaron shall cast lots upon the Two
Goats one lot for the Lord and the other
lot for the
scapegoat the one um the one lot that
fall on uh uh as the skate goat that'll
be the goat that's going to be used to
be the skapegoat that's going to be uh
used for this offering okay go ahead and
Aaron shall bring the goat upon which
the Lord lot fail and offer him for a
sin offering but the goat on which the
lot fail to be the scapegoat shall be
presented alive before the Lord to make
an atonement with him and to let him go
for a scapegoat Into the Wilderness yeah
so just just imagine when you taking a
rifle or let's just imagine that you got
two sticks one stick is long one stick
is short and the uh long stick fell on
uh the long stick is the stick for the
skapegoat and when that stickers pull
that's the one okay for that for the for
the uh goat that's gonna be the
scapegoat all right that that's all I
got if anybody want to add
something all right I think you hit it
real good there brother hope that
answered they question as we move on to
our next moving on uh just no ask why
did Abraham give his wife away twice
lied and say she was his sister in
Genesis
12: 10 through 20 and Genesis 20 veres
1-18 but instead of punishing
Abraham God punished the Kings and
Abraham received gifts what's the
lesson brother Julius what's the lesson
well let's answer the question first
let's go to Genesis chapter 12 and let's
make a correction on two parts of this
question first of all Abraham didn't
give Sarah away either time number two
he uh he didn't lie about Sarah being
his sister she was his sister let's go
and let's look at what the Bible says
that way we have to interpret and put
things there that ought not to be
Genesis chapter 12 Genesis 12 brother
James instead of starting at verse 10
let's start at verse 11 and let the
Bible answer this question go ahead okay
and it came to pass when he was come
near to enter into Egypt that he said
unto Sarah his wife behold now I know
that thou art a fair woman to look upon
uhhuh therefore it shall come to pass
when the Egyptians shall see thee that
they shall say this is his wife and they
will kill me but they will save thee
alive they will save you alive because
Abraham believed that the Egyptian was
going to kill him and take his wife but
go ahead and read say I pray thee Thou
Art my sister that it may be well with
me for thy sake and my soul shall live
because of thee and my soul shall live
because of he so he prophesied and it
happened and it came to pass that when
Pharaoh did come to her what happened to
Sarah what happened what happened to
Sarah go ahead let's continue quickly
and it came pass that when Abram was
coming to Egypt the Egyptians beheld the
woman that she was very fair the
princess also of pharaoh saw her and
commanded her before pharaoh and the
woman and the woman was taken into
Pharaoh's house so Sarah was taken
Abraham didn't give her away she was
taken and and to to and look what
happened Abraham said they're going to
treat me well read verse 16 just the top
of that go ahead and he entreated Abram
well for her sake uh and he and he end
up getting some uh gifts and asses and
Men Serv and Ma servants so now let's go
to Genesis chapter 20 okay I'm
there Genesis 20 this time this time my
brother pick it up at verse one go ahead
and Abram soured from then toward the
South Country and dwelt between cadesh
and Sher and soured in gah go ahead and
Abram said of Sarah his wife she is my
sister and aimc king of Gage sent and
took Sarah the first thing we heard
about when Sarah when they was in Egypt
now they're in aara and ailec is the
king of gar go ahead and God came to
ailec in minute I'm sorry I went too
fast read verse two again quickly and
Abram said of of S of of Sarah his wife
she is my sister and AMC king of G sent
and took her so Abraham didn't give her
away just like she was taken by the
Egyptians she was taken by the king of
ailec go ahead but God came to ailec in
a Dream by night and said to him behold
Thou Art but a dead man for the woman
which thou has taken for she is a man's
wife so the Lord had straightened it out
with the King and to give him back his
wife so now why did Abraham do this SK
down to verse 11 and go ahead and Abram
said because I thought surely the fear
of God is not in this place and they
will slay me for my wife's sake and they
will slay they will kill me for Sarah's
sake go ahead and yet indeed she is my
sister she is the daughter of my father
but not the daughter of my mother and
she became my wife because there was uh
you go to the Book of Genesis you'll
find out that the children married each
other the brothers and sisters married
each other so Abra Sarah was Abraham's
sister and she became his wife that's
all I got now the end of that what was
what is the lesson out of this the
Lord showed you that Abraham was the
father of the faithful he believed God
he obeyed God and he took care of
Abraham and made everybody else take
care of Abraham that's all I got in
there and brother Julius BC Knew Too not
to touch another man's wife didn't he he
said surely I thought the fear of the
Lord but the Lord came and he would have
took Sarah but the Lord came and fixed
that thing
yeah all right thank you for that hope
that answered that question as we move
to our next our next one amazing
Israelites Israelite asked will the
silence in heaven mentioned in
Revelation the a perod of the Saints
being changed and rewarded
the elders mention in
Revelation is that a look at what will
be after the first
resurrection brother Jerome shed some
light on the
silence no the the the silence it takes
place
before uh the change which is in the
first resurrection okay so um let's go
to that um Revelations 8 I'm there where
it's mentioned and read verse 1 and
two and when he had opened the seventh
seal there was silence in heaven about
the space of half an hour stop right
there right there now uh it says silence
for a space of a half an hour whatever
that silence is I don't know okay but uh
it said and when the seven seal cuz it's
seven seals all together all those seals
got to be broken before you even get to
the trumpets and there seven of them and
Jesus don't come and the resurrection
don't happen and those in the first
resurrection don't get changed until the
seven trumpet is
blown okay so all the seals got to be
broken first then you got seven angels
getting seven trumpets okay so this
silence happened long before that seven
trumpet when those in the first
resurrection going to get changed okay
so now
uh go ahead and read and I saw the seven
angels which stood before God and to
them were given seven
trumpets now let's deal with the second
question read that again sister
de okay the second question was
um the elders mention in
Revelation is that a a look at what will
be after the first resurrection
okay now that that that's a yes that's a
yes because the elders you know uh they
actually don't come out of the Grave
because that's where they at right now
and they won't their graves until
that first resurrection which takes
place at the blowing of the seven
trumpet
okay but the Lord is calling that which
is not as though it is because he know
it's gonna happen okay all right so now
let's go to uh the 11th chapter of
Revelations and read verse
15-8 uh Revelation 11: 15-18 says and
the seventh Angels sounded and there
were great voices in heaven saying the
kingdoms of this world are become the
kingdoms of our Lord and of his Christ
and he shall reign forever and ever and
the four and 20 the 4 and 20 Elders
which set before God on their seats fell
upon their faces and worshiped God
saying we give thanks oh Lord God
Almighty which art and was and art to
come because thou has taken to thee
great power and has
reigned Verse 18 oh I'm sorry and the
nations were angry and thy wrath has
come in the time of the Dead that they
should be judged and that thou should us
give reward unto thy servants the
prophets and to the the Saints and them
that fear thy name small and great and
should as destroy them which destroy the
Earth yeah so that take place after that
seven trumpet that's all I
get all right thank you for that brother
hope that answered their question as we
move on to our next one yeah they also
asked saying my 12y old would like to
know if you can be friends with Sunday
worshippers
sure you can as long as you
are GED with the truth also I mean I
have friends of different Faith but um
but I'm Gerty with the truth but let's
go into Deuteronomy 11th on behalf of
your 12y old Deuteronomy
11 okay because in order to stay away
from people of other Faith hey you would
just about have to be taken out of the
world but the Lord say he pray not that
we are taken out of the world but that
we are kept from the world Deuteronomy
11 and read that verse one when you get
there
brother therefore shalt love thou shalt
love the Lord thy God and keep his
charge and his statutes and his
judgments and his Commandments always so
it's good to make sure your 12 year old
is GED with this information here skip
down read 18 and 19 go
ahead therefore shall ye lay up these my
words in your heart and in your soul and
bind them for a sign upon your hand that
they may be as frontlets between your
eyes and ye shall teach them your
children speaking of them when thou sest
in thine house and when thou walst by
the way and when thou liest down and
when thou risest up and that is a good
way to make sure that your 12y old is gy
with his word of God and with his true
because we teach our 12 year olds at the
class and they are girded with the word
of God now let's turn over quickly to
Proverbs 22 and
6 Proverbs 22 and
6 22 and six okay go ahead train up a
child in the way he should go and when
he is old he will not depart from it so
those are some good weapons that you
give your 12y old and yeah they can be
friends they just have to you know be
strong in the Lord for sure that's all I
got and we hope that that answers your
question as we move on to our next one
next one
Desmond Marshall asks is the cross
considered an idol or is the cross
considered a holy image because Jesus
was crucified on
it D what you say yeah the cross is not
a holy image no it is a Graven image and
people do bow down to it and they kiss
it and they look deal with the image
that's on it or off of it let's go to
Exodus 20 Exodus 20 and pick it up at
verse three Exodus 20 we're going to
read 3 to5 okay
Thou shalt have nor the gods before me
Thou shalt not make unto thee any Graven
image or any likeness of anything that
is in heaven above or that is in the
earth beneath or that is in the water
under the Earth Thou shalt not bow down
thyself to them nor serve them for I the
Lord thy God am a jealous God visiting
the iniquity of the fathers upon the
children until the third and fourth
generation of them that hate me yes so
the the cross is an image that people
bow down to they wear it around their
neck as a holy instrument it is not that
Jesus wasn't the only one that died on
the cross we have some history that
will'll be getting into in the month of
February that will break down how many
people died daily on the
cross even says the crosses were never
bear it is not a holy image it has
become a Graven image of worship and
know we shouldn't have it that's all I
got all right thank you for that brother
hope that answered that question as we
move on to our next one next one
Jennifer Love says
is is
there if there will be no more death in
my misreading
Ezekiel
47:12 and Isaiah
65:20 if there will be no more death
brother
Jerome and there will be no more death
um in the father's Kingdom but those two
verses you referring to let's go take a
look at them and see if that's talking
about the father's Kingdom
okay Ezekiel
47-12 okay
and by the river upon the bank thereof
on this side and on that side shall grow
all trees for meat whose Leaf shall not
fade neither shall the fruit thereof be
consumed it shall bring forth new fruit
according to his months because their
Waters they issued out of the sanctuary
and the fruit thereof shall be for meat
and the leaf thereof for medicine so in
the son's Kingdom you gonna have flesh
and blood and there going to be times
where they going to need some
medicine that's in the son's Kingdom but
in the father's Kingdom if there ain't
no more death they not going to need no
medicine but that don't change the fact
that then these trees GNA still be there
and they still going to be bearing fruit
and uh in Revelation it said they were
for the healing other nations but in the
father's Kingdom they're not going to be
needed but they still going to be there
cuz in the son's Kingdom they was used
for
not in the fathers okay so now let's go
to that uh Isaiah
65 I'm
there therefore shall no more then an
infant of days nor an old man that has
not filled his days for the child shall
die and 100 years old but the sinner
being a 100 years old shall be a cursed
now once again that's in the son's
Kingdom it's not the father's Kingdom
because there ain't going to be no more
death in the father's Kingdom according
to Revelations 21 all right cuz Jesus
got to deliver up the kingdom first so
let's go read that let's go to 1
Corinthians chapter
15 he GNA reain for a thousand years
okay and get the kingdom prepared for
the father to to deliver it to the
father so 1 Corinthians 15 pick it up at
verse
25 read to the 26
okay for he must Reign till Heath put
all enemies under his feet The Last
Enemy that shall be destroyed is
death so it said The Last Enemy that
shall be destroyed is death so he got a
rain and the last thing he got to put
under his feet is death okay so now read
that verse
24 then cometh the end when he shall
have delivered up the kingdom to God
even the father when he shall have put
down all Rule and all authority and
power all right now go to Revelations 20
quickly Revelation 20 read verse
11-4 Revelation 20: 11-14 says and I saw
a great white throne and him that sat on
it from whose face the earth and the
heaven fled away and there was found the
Lord got to do this he got to prepare he
got to get everything and put everything
under his feet so this judgment day this
is the son's Kingdom he getting it
prepared for the father go ahead and
there was found no place for them and I
saw the dead small and great stand
before God and the books were open and
another book was open which is The Book
of Life and the dead were judged out of
those things which were written in the
books according to their Works uhuh and
the Sea gave up the dead which were in
it and death and Hell delivered up the
the dead which were in them and they
were judged every man according to their
Works come and death and hell were cast
into the Lake of Fire this is the second
death Last Enemy was death right so now
go right into the 2st chapter now we
going to us in the he gonna present the
kingdom to the father and there ain't
going to be no more death cuz he it was
thrown in the Lake of Fire death and H
go ahead one one through four and
that'll be it and I saw a new heaven and
a new Earth for the first Heaven and the
first Earth were passed away and there
was no more sea and I John saw the holy
city New Jerusalem coming down from God
out of Heaven prepared as a bride
adorned for her husband and I heard a
great voice out of Heaven saying behold
the Tabernacle of God is with men and he
shall dwell with them and they shall be
his people and God himself shall be with
them and be their God
and God shall wipe away all tears from
their eyes and there shall be no more
death neither sorrow nor crying neither
shall there be any more pain for the
former things are passed away that's
that's all I
get all right thank you for that brother
hope that answered that question next
question with a Time Check Yes time is
8:41 and credit account says I have no
scripture for this question but
regarding Elijah the tishbite and
Jezebel was she a hamite so they want to
know the question is Jezebel was she and
hamite you're wrong yeah uh yes she was
she was a Canaanite which is or one of
the families out of the hamites okay so
let's go take a look at it let's go to
First Kings chapter 16 read verse
31 okay verse 31 says and it came to
pass as if it had been a light thing for
him to walk in the sins of jeroboam the
son of nebat that he took to wife
Jezebel the daughter of Ethel king of
zidonians and went and served baale and
worship
to so you know that's ahab's wife jeze
and he said she was uh of the daughter
of fvl King of the zidonians and the
zidonians is uh you can trace them right
on up to ham okay so she a hamite one
more place and that be at First
Chronicles verse one chapter 1 I'm sorry
chapter 1 verse 13 Veron one okay verse
13 says and Canan begat zidon his
firstborn and Heth yeah that's all I
got all right thank you for that as we
move on to our next question next
question and they also ask if you want
to start a business do you have to pay
tithes on profits the business makes or
the money you pay yourself as
income all right guest caller
if you're the soul owner of the business
then every every profit you make in the
business is
yours all that simple let's go uh uh uh
quickly to uh Genesis the 14th chapter
and we're going to read verses 18 to 20
let me see how much of uh ties that uh
uh uh Abraham pay the mil day okay
Genesis 14 verses 18 to 20 says and
mesed king of Salem brought forth Bread
and Wine and he was the priest of the
most high God and he blessed him and
said Blessed Be Abram of the most high
god possessor of Heaven and Earth and
blessed be the most high God which had
delivered thine enemies into thine hand
and he gave them he gave him tithes of
all he gave him TI of all didn't he yes
y That's whatever that's that mean that
whatever you whatever you had your
income of all go to Genesis the 28th
chapter read vers
20 through uh
uh
22 Genesis 28 verses 20- 22 says and
Jacob vowed a vow saying if God will be
with me and will keep me in this way
that I go and will give me bread to eat
and rment to put on so that I come again
to my father's house in peace then shall
the Lord be my God and this Stone which
I have set for a pillar shall be God's
house and all that thou shalt give me I
will surely give the tenth unto
thee he says that word again to all that
mean that whatever you got no matter no
matter whether you got it proper through
business deal whether you paid yourself
a salary if it all come to you you're
supposed to give him a tenth of all of
it one other place and that's it let's
go into uh uh Proverbs 3 and read verse
9 Proverbs
3 and verse n says honor the Lord with
thy substance and with the first fruits
of all thine
increase I in love with thy substance
with the first fruit of all thy increase
so if you're the sole owner of the
business you don't have no partners and
nobody to split the profit with whatever
your profit is you're supposed to give
God is
10% all
right hope that answered your question
is we move on to our next one as time is
ticking yes uh Zion says when Heaven is
finally on Earth how will we be living
like will we have families and houses
and live like we do
now but without sin does the Bible speak
about those things all right when Heaven
is finally on Earth they say guess
calling first thing is Earth is heaven
it's the first heaven right and where
the find the stars and moon and the
clouds and all that's heaven and where
God dwell that's the third heaven so
let's rephrase that when God when Jesus
and God come to
Earth let show you Jesus Kingdom first
let's go into Isaiah 65th
chapter and read vers 17 to
21 Isaiah 65 vers 17- 21 says for behold
I create new heavens and a new Earth and
the former shall not be remembered no
nor come into mind but be ye glad and
rejoiced forever in that which I create
for behold I create Jerusalem a
rejoicing and her people a joy and I
will rejoice in Jerusalem and joy in my
people and the voice of weeping shall be
no more heard in her nor the voice of
crying there shall be no more then an
infant of day nor an old man that have
not filled his days for the child shall
die 100 years old but the sinner being
100 years old shall be
accursed so now you going to have death
and you going to have sin during Jesus
kingdom was that the end of
that uh that was the end of
20 go ahead keep reading and they shall
build houses and inhabit them and they
shall plant Vineyards and eat the fruit
thereof
22 go ahead 22 says they should not
build in other inhabitant they should
not plant and eat and another eat for as
the days of a tree are the days of my
people and my elect shall long enjoy the
work of their
hands so they going to have children
they're going to build houses and
somebody's going to be committing sin
that's doing Jesus Kingdom right the
father's kingdom is different they a't
going to have no
children and you ain't going to be
building no hous you ain't going to have
no and you and uh uh you won't be
committing sin because there'll be no
more death let's go quickly to
Revelation the 21st
chapter and read 1-
4 okay Revelation 21: 1-4 says and I saw
a new Heaven and new Earth for the first
Heaven and the first Earth were passed
away and there was no more sea and I
John saw the holy city New Jerusalem
coming down from God out of Heaven
prepared as a bride adorned for her
husband and I heard a great voice out of
Heaven saying behold the Tabernacle of
God is with men and he will dwell with
them and they shall be his people and
God himself shall be with them and be
their God and God shall wipe away all
tears from their eyes and there shall be
no more death neither sorrow nor crying
neither shall there be any more pain for
the former things are passed
away that's the father's King ain't
going to have no children Ain going to
need no houses and ain't going to be no
more dying and no
sin that's all I have to say all right
hope that answered your question as we
move on to our next one ah yes anneal
Dan said has help me to understand the
meaning of double portion of thy Spirit
be upon me and they give First Kings 2
verse 9 First Kings 2 verse 9 double
portion sounds very good to me what you
say brother Julius oh man the the
definition of a double portion is
something that's uh twice given it is
given twice to others
you want a cheeseburger that's a single
Patty a double cheeseburger is a double
Patty so that's a double portion he's
asking for a double portion of el um
Elicia is asking for a double portion
let's go to second king First Kings 2
and read verse 9 First Kings 2 James and
verse 9 when you get it brother read it
first Kings 2 I thought Second Kings I'm
sorry First Kings 2
verse is it Second Kings or they gave
First Kings they gave for First Kings
but Second Kings 9 2 and9 is where it
says a double portion let's let's go to
Second Kings thank you brother Second
Kings 9 and when you get it go ahead and
read it at verse two and it came to pass
when they were gone over that Elijah
said unto Elisha ask what I shall do for
thee before I be taken away from thee
and Alisha said I pray thee let a double
portion of thy Spirit be upon me so now
the Lord uh uh he he asked Elicia and he
gave him the sign and yes he did give
him a double portion Elisha Elijah did a
lot of
signs and Elisha did double those signs
and more so but he gave him a double
portion of his spirit so yes that's what
he
meant yes sir instead of one p you get
two right brother jul man more
responsibility but the bottom line is he
did more thing that Elisha Elijah did
but he asked for that and it was granted
to him yes sir thank you for that
brother sister Deborah next question
next question is from ANC H as in Acts
28 verse 21 the elders say we have not
received your letters are they talking
about the letters that Paul has in the
Bible
Jerome no um let's go read it though uh
verse
um verse
21 let's read it and they said unto him
we neither received Letters Out of Judea
concerning thee neither any of the
Brethren that came showed or spake any
harm of thee yeah uh he was really
talking about letters concerning uh what
you read in verse 17- 20 so let's read
that um verse
17-2 okay and it came to pass that after
three days Paul called the chief of the
Jews together and when they were come
together he said unto them men and
Brethren though I have committed nothing
against the people or customs of our
fathers yet was I delivered prisoner
from Jerusalem into the hands of the
Romans who when they had examined me
would have let me go because there was
no cause of death in me but when the
Jews spake against it I was constrained
to appeal unto Caesar not that I had
ought to accuse my nation of for this
cause therefore have I called for you to
see you and to speak with you because
that for the hope of Israel I am bound
with this chain yeah and they was saying
well we ain't see no letters concerning
none of this
you know that's what it was about that's
all I
got all right thank you for that
Brothers we move on to our next question
Deborah is time is a ticket yes time is
ticking and the next question is from
melon uh natural
Journey uh she asked as far as
marriage as far as marriage goes can we
go to the just of the peace or do we
have to get married in a
church well lots of people go to the
justice of the peace and some people get
married in the church too um it's your
choice but you need to know what
marriage vows are let's just read a
little bit Ephesians 5 right quick
Ephesians the 5th
chapter when you get there brother pick
it up at that verse 20 for me Ephesians
5 and
20 okay Ephesians 5 and 20 says giving
thanks always for all things unto God
and the father in the name of our Lord
Jesus
Christ submitting yourselves one to
another in the fear of
God wives submit yourselves unto your
own husbands as unto the Lord for the
husband is the head of the wife even as
Christ is the head of the church and he
is the savior of the
body therefore as the church is subject
unto Christ so let the H so let the
wives be to their own husbands and
everything husbands love your wives even
as Christ also loved the church and gave
himself for it that he might read read
32 gave himself for it go ahead brother
32 says this is a great mystery but I
speak concerning Christ and the church
yes and this is a great mystery and it's
good to have a marriage done with a
truth be told because you'll get some of
the vows and requirement of God also and
not every Justice of the Peace do it but
get your license getting the paper is
key and uh it's really your choice
that's all I
got as we move on to our next question
with time ticking because we having fun
go ahead yes uh n c
HS um in Acts 19 verses
3-5 why did Paul have to baptize them
again Acts 19 verse 3-5 when you get
there brother and the guest caller shed
some light on why did Paul have to
baptize them
again okay acts 19: 3-5 says and he said
unto them unto what then were ye
baptized and they said unto John's
baptism then said Paul John verily
baptized with the baptism of repentance
saying unto the people that they should
believe on him which should come after
him that is on Christ Jesus when they
heard this they were baptized in the
name of the Lord
Jesus well that's why they had to get
rebap tized
because Jesus had gave a commandment
let's go to Matthew 28th chapter and
read vers 16- 19 right
three Matthew
28:
16-19 says then the 11 disciples went
away into Galilee into a mountain where
Jesus has Appo had appointed them and
when they saw him they worshiped him but
some doubted and Jesus came and spake
unto them saying all power is given un
to me in heaven and in Earth go ye
therefore and teach All Nations
baptizing them in the name of the father
and of the son and of the Holy
Ghost okay now the word repentant is not
a
name that's changing your way we said go
baptizing in the name of the
father and the Son and the Holy Ghost so
a name had to be called on him so they's
see why Jesus man let's go to St John 5
and read
43 St John 5 and
43 5 and 43 says I am come in my
father's name and you receive me not if
another shall come in his own name him
ye will
receive so Jesus came in his father's
name go to John 14 and read verse
26 John
14 and verse 26 says but the comforter
which is the Holy Ghost whom the father
will send in my name he shall teach you
all things and bring all things to your
remembrance whatsoever I have said unto
you who the Lord told you to go baptize
in the name of the Father the Son and
the Holy Ghost Jesus came in the
father's name that mean the father's
name was Jesus and that made Jesus uh uh
uh carry his name which is Jesus and he
going to send you the holy SP spirit in
Jesus name that's why the name that you
should be baptized in is Jesus that's
why it had to be be baptized again
because they had to have a name called
over that's all I have to say that's
right all right sister deil let's do one
more question and we have ran out of
time all right uh yes so the next
question is just know ask in
madak Genesis 14: 18-2 20 and and the
God who spoke to Abraham are both
manifestations of
Jesus why did he appear in different
forms what was the
purpose all right guess
caller where is it written that he
appeared in different
forms that's all I have to say yep so
with leave that question right there as
we say that we have officially ran out
of time yes the time is
901 all right we'd like to thank
everybody from all around the world who
tuned in with us and sent in those
questions we enjoy taking part in
answering them if you submitted a
question and we didn't get to it don't
worry we will take that question sister
Deborah put it in rotation and we will
deal with that question next week so
until we all come together again be safe
be blessed stay prayed up and may the
Lord have mercy on us all as brother
James closes us out Our Father which art
in heaven Hallowed be thy name thy
kingdom come thy will be done in earth
as it is in heaven give us this day our
daily bread and forgive us our debts as
we forgive our debtors and lead us not
into temptation but Deliver Us from from
Evil for thine is the kingdom and the
power and the glory forever in Jesus
name we pray amen